There's much movement because we had a gamification and it would just display it directly from here
So this is just a reminder posture could sleep preparation
and I'll add a few features. I have more open multiple extensions
so if I wanted to open a cursor and let's make it open my Chrome extension tab
and I will use JVTim. Alright, we'll return to our agent mode and first what I'm going to do
because now I see there is a movement break that we show us to apply it like
but when I press 10 it doesn't apply so I want to change it because even if I want to play like
a customer or a community doesn't apply so I'll open this primary open here
I want to get an issue because when I try to add a custom time to my reminders it doesn't
and doesn't process, it should be processed when I type a number and press enter
and I'll open your agent for minders please add a time counter but we'll check every second
and display time of reminder and I'll go back again the next tension and probably I will
just make it a little bit concise it should be around with the X so I can press this
you can select this, it will be visible, I'll go back to a cursor it should be in the
first marker so it should now work but first I'll just add the feature it's examining
the current minder implementation dot count on timer it's an account on timer to each
reminder card is updated code and display the time of the next reminder seems like it's
co-clating and now I think this is a styling okay we see it at the timer was the timer
we have some functionalities, I will now refresh it and I want to go back okay it's starting
is disabled, timing every minute it's starting so we'll go back again instead of updating
counter it shows only starting I'll just post it I don't think I need the description
I would make it more concise in one line because many people maybe would have two more
so I can just remove the description put everyone minute to the right same for 40 seconds
and here to the app so I will place it again go to the cursor is this as an exemption
this is time counter or this fixed custom time is this line of reordering so the reminder of the on the left should stay the same but
the timer picker should be on the right then then I can't tell the current time and option toggle on the right
but everything in one line so more reminders than it is paid
the main on the window
the problem is I don't see this reminder because it's now every minute but we don't see it
especially when it's prompt because yeah I'll post the video and return when it's like zero it
just will pop up the one window that is here but I want a bigger reminder and that reminder
should have an image in options for example that option should display and sound and maybe lower
right corner some of the notification to post your check yeah oh I think it's automatically changing
now I see every minute okay doing now
okay now it's changing okay I will change it a little bit the design it's sometimes we don't see
everything and I will just remove the prefix which is the every it will prefix every and make
toggle a little bit smaller so go back again apply some design results so remove prefix from
there it is from frame press from time until it is there it is the prefix is a very and toggle
button make a little bit smaller but when it hover you can get nice animation
and now at your agent when activity is due you can start counting the game but when it's too
and start and finish and when it's due and finish accounting I would like to have a sound
to be played to define user and the application at the very low right button
and when the friends exit so this will actually work can work right
so it will try to fix the custom and then you to try to use the dashboard
and obviously when we edit I would like to have another thing which is the settings settings is
allowed us to see because I see only the dashboard and the posture check or dashboard we can
change okay we see it's radi updating the dynamic game it's doing now we're going to open dashboard
we have here again everything and so the notification shows the reminder in the description
clicking it can open extension you you can handle that probably will walk and now it can open
so it works as intended we see that nice animation daily moment break in the real fasting
probably we can make it a little bit like a more in line
okay maybe we can put in the two liners because it's still having will not have enough place
but even when we hover we have stay hydrated which is a good thing so for that case
and I can go to cursor or remove it make and press for reminders and two lines
so in in line in the first line will be in name activity
and toggle bottom but they will be a timer settings and active time of time
and when you isolate and settings stop in both and allow me to change between dark and
light mode and select sound of notification
all right so now it should work I will change it maybe to 30 minutes
and probably we'll leave it for now and there are some websites that can be blocked
for our activities so I can stay free website blocker that will research our results because
previously not sure if you remember if I open my hello longevity extension
the full dashboard there are some settings now browser notification achievements goes
and we have a progress here
the fabrics one we can remove that from here reminders all right I think contact
I would just make it a little bit dynamic so I'd access feed for it and we can make a notification
okay now I think it's better so it shows the time I have settings now
can switch between dark okay I love it we can see all the extensions for example if I add brief
extension we can get some inspiration right there so there is a brief and I will go to their page
so it's free
so we can test how it looks like I will go to the extension
how it is a brief I can not continue with Google
so I think on my extensions not open while they even monetize it so we have like a
yellowy and dashboard and now if I open it up it's a nice design I like it and we can switch
that design and try to see dynamic some breaks activate the week it's personalized manage focus
we can do some website blocking background noise and although this pay practice is like breathing
so if I press it now it's time for breathing so we can actually copy this we can actually get
inspired by that so there's more journal when we can set up our more journal and breathing
and we can copy this so first I want to check this design to simulate the similar things like
here I'll go to cursor and open new agent change design this something similar to it
and then I can open new agent and add like new models so the one will be breathing with animation
and that one will be a cursor you can enter breathing mode with timer and follow instructions
that will open only in a new page
it's just example I don't want to copy that Chrome extension because it's just not nice to copy all of it
so there are obviously other possibilities that you can use in that extension there is a focus
so we can add some background noise that we can play and obviously it can be played in a background
so you can play it here so you cannot play a mood profile so obviously you can apply
mood journal to and get our report so the background noise can be implemented too
and yeah if I have a new agent add a new tab background noise and allow us to play
and we can for relaxing noise working or went down relaxing and down
so now we'll add like a few free new features for our own job in extension
and I would just ask for one thing, error says about the code
so we have like a top longevity error says fits and we can obviously add error says fit for
longevity and use it because for example this is the fit if I open it out we'll be able to use
the reader error says reader and here we have some of the information that we can use and we can
create a big website about it
okay so how we use the one that we have here
versus fit nice when I open it and I'll add it to our add addresses reader to be updated
with longevity use use this fit okay so this is the example thing and now when I go back open my
extension well then it looks like we much better we see dynamics we see hours time the profile
the brakes can create a breathing mode so we can copy the AI and design so now we have even
some breathing exercise that we can use perfectly that add our features so this time we can
reinvent or implement it for our case even when I press the dashboard I think yeah
it will update so there are background events
we have some sound but keep that in mind we can have our custom hours in our way with like 11 laps
notification sounds bell, two months so this one will help us with gamification
there are some reminders let me see I think it's building still a RSS parser for the information
so it will improve HTML and it is the code in it and then after that we will get
some of the work in service worker context
okay so it's fetches RSS actually I'm curious it's more complicated but it probably
can do it directly there so I'll clear all of it pop up now and when I go here open our use
to refresh and load articles from the new spell but not sure if it's loading
okay okay so the RSS is still not working but no worries we'll get them so just copy this
go to our cursor I hear the next session so it's working now
and allow this console error and implement this
I think the one I won't implement as well is just typing Jason on this function so we'll go there
okay we hear it if you're breathing focus dynamics breaks news
okay we replace them parser or decode HTML should work I'll open it reload it
and yeah I see the news right and I can refresh it by pressing and see some of the information
so now it's being manipulated we did the thing that allowed us to do it we added like
breathing journal new tab there is another extension like dashboard we have a mood journal
we can implement switch warm up I didn't want to add it I decided the breathing so the only
breathing now is for them it just doesn't look like great as it's supposed to and we have similar
function all this